<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>juk.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Џук</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Џук</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxJuKxx</name>
  <summary>Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Reproductor musical</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Přehrávač hudby</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Musikafspiller</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Audio-Wiedergabe</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Muusikamängija</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Musiikkisoitin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Zenelejátszó</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Musikafspeler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Muziekspeler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz muzyki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Leitor de Música</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Reprodutor de músicas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Prehrávač hudby</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Glasbeni predvajalnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Музички плејер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Muzički plejer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Музички плејер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Muzički plejer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Musikspelare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Музичний програвач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxMusic Playerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>JuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El JuK és una aplicació de màquina de discos musicals, que accepta col·leccions de fitxers d'àudio MP3, Ogg Vorbis, i FLAC. Permet editar les "etiquetes" dels fitxers d'àudio, i gestionar les col·leccions i les llistes de reproducció. De fet, els seu focus principal és en la gestió de la música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">JuK er et lydjukebox-program, som understøtter samlinger af MP3-, Ogg Vorbis- og FLAC-lydfiler. Den lader dig redigere "mærkerne" i dine lydfiler og håndtere din samling og spillelister. Dens hovedfokus er faktisk på musikhåndtering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">JuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">JuK es una aplicación jukebox de audio, que soporta colecciones de archivos MP3, Ogg Vorbis y FLAC. Le permite editar los "tags" de sus archivos de audio, y administrar sus colecciones y listas de reproducción. Su principal cometido, de hecho, es administrar la música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">JuK on helifailide muusikamängija, mis toetab MP3, Ogg Vorbise ja FLAC-i vormingut. See võimaldab muuta helifailide "silte" ning hallata muusikakogusid ja esitusnimekirju. Õigupoolest ongi rakenduse rõhk eelkõige muusika haldamisel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A JuK egy zenedoboz alkalmazás, amely támogatja MP3, Ogg Vorbis és FLAC hangfájlok gyűjteményeit. Lehetővé teszi a hangfájlok „címkéinek” szerkesztését, és a gyűjtemények, illetve lejátszólisták kezelését. A fő célja valójában a zenekezelés.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">JuK is en Musikkist-Programm, dat Sammeln vun MP3-, Ogg-Vorbis- un FLAC-Klangdateien bruken kann. Du kannst dor de Slötelwöör („Tags“) vun Dien Dateien mit bewerken un Dien Sammeln un Afspeellisten mit plegen. Egens liggt em sien Fokus redig op de Musikpleeg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">JuK is een jukebox toepassing voor geluid, die verzamelingen van MP3, Ogg Vorbis en FLAC geluidsbestanden ondersteunt. Het stelt u in staat om de "tags" van uw geluidsbestanden te bewerken en uw verzameling en afspeellijsten te beheren. De focus is in feite op beheer van muziek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">JuK jest programem szafy grającej, obsługującym zbiory MP3, Ogg Vorbis oraz pliki dźwiękowe FLAC. Umożliwia edytowanie "znaczników" plików dźwiękowych i zarządzanie zbiorami oraz listami odtwarzania. Jednak jego głównym celem jest zarządzanie muzyką.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O JuK é uma aplicação de reprodução de música, suportando colecções de ficheiros de áudio em MP3, Ogg Vorbis e FLAC. Permite-lhe editar as "marcas" dos seus ficheiros de áudio, gerir a sua colecção e as suas listas de reprodução. O seu foco principal é, de facto, a gestão de música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">JuK é um aplicativo para reprodução de músicas, com suporte a coleções de arquivos de áudio MP3, Ogg Vorbis e FLAC. Permite-lhe editar as etiquetas "tags" dos seus arquivos de áudio, gerenciar sua coleção e suas listas de músicas. Seu foco principal é, de fato, o gerenciamento de músicas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">JuK je aplikácia hudobného jukeboxu, podporujúca kolekcie MP3, Ogg Vorbis a FLAC audio súborov. Umožní vám upraviť tagy vašich audio súborov a spravovať vašu kolekciu a zoznamy skladieb. Jeho hlavné zameranie je správa hudby.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">JuK je predvajalnik glasbe, ki podpira zbirke zvočnih datotek MP3, Ogg Vorbis in FLAC. Omogoča urejanje "oznak" vaših zvočnih datotek ter upravljanje zbirk in seznamov predvajanj. Glavni name programa je upravljanje glasbe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Џук је програм за виртуелни џубокс. Подржава збирке МП3, ОГГ, ворбис и ФЛАЦ аудио фајлова. Даје вам да уређујете „ознаке“ аудио фајлова, и управљате збиркама и листама нумера. Тежиште му је, у ствари, на управљању музиком.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Juk je program za virtuelni džuboks. Podržava zbirke MP3, OGG, Vorbis i FLAC audio fajlova. Daje vam da uređujete „oznake“ audio fajlova, i upravljate zbirkama i listama numera. Težište mu je, u stvari, na upravljanju muzikom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Џук је програм за виртуелни џубокс. Подржава збирке МП3, ОГГ, ворбис и ФЛАЦ аудио фајлова. Даје вам да уређујете „ознаке“ аудио фајлова, и управљате збиркама и листама нумера. Тежиште му је, у ствари, на управљању музиком.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Juk je program za virtuelni džuboks. Podržava zbirke MP3, OGG, Vorbis i FLAC audio fajlova. Daje vam da uređujete „oznake“ audio fajlova, i upravljate zbirkama i listama numera. Težište mu je, u stvari, na upravljanju muzikom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Juk är ett Jukebox-program, som stöder samlingar av MP3, Ogg Vorbis och FLAC ljudfiler. Det låter dig redigera "taggarna" i ljudfilerna, och hantera samlingen och spellistor. Dess huvudfokus är just musikhantering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">JuK — програма для відтворення музики, у якій передбачено підтримку роботи зі звуковими файлами у форматах MP3, Ogg Vorbis та FLAC. Програма допоможе вам у редагуванні міток ваших звукових файлів, керуванні вашою збіркою та списками відтворення. Основним її призначенням, фактично, є керування музичними даними.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxJuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Collection list and multiple user defined playlists</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Llista de col·leccions i múltiples llistes de reproducció definides per usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Samlingsliste og flere brugerdefinerede spillelister</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Collection list and multiple user defined playlists</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Listas de colecciones y listas de reproducción definidas por múltiples usuarios</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Muusikakogu nimekiri ja paljud kasutaja loodud esitusnimekirjad</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Gyűjteménylista és több felhasználó által megadott lejátszólista</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Sammelnlist un en Reeg Bruker-Afspeellisten</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verzamelingenlijst en afspeellijsten voor meerdere gebruikers</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Spisy zbiorów i wiele list odtwarzania określonych przez użytkownika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Lista de colecções e várias listas de reprodução definidas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Lista de coleções e várias listas de músicas definidas pelo usuário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zoznam kolekcií a viacnásobné používateľom definované zoznamy skladieb</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Seznam zbirk in več uporabniško določenih seznamov predvajanja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Листа збирки и више кориснички дефинисаних листа нумера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Lista zbirki i više korisnički definisanih lista numera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Листа збирки и више кориснички дефинисаних листа нумера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Lista zbirki i više korisnički definisanih lista numera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Samlingslista och flera användardefinierade spellistor.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Список збірки та декілька визначених користувачем списків відтворення.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCollection list and multiple user defined playlistsxx</li>
      <li>Ability to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start up</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Capacitat d'explorar directoris per importar automàticament llistes de reproducció i fitxers de música en iniciar-se</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Kan scanne mapper for automatisk at importere spillelister og musikfiler ved opstart</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Ability to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start up</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capacidad de escanear directorios para importar listas de reproducción y archivos de música automáticamente al iniciar el programa</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Oskus uurida kohe käivitamisel läbi katalooge ja importida sealt esitusnimekirju ja muusikafaile</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Könyvtárak átvizsgálásának képessége zenefájlok és lejátszólisták automatikus importálásához a program indulásakor</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann Ornern  bi't Starten automaatsch op Afspeellisten un Musikdateien dörkieken</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheid om bij opstarten mappen te scannen om automatisch afspeellijsten en muziekbestanden te importeren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość przeszukiwania katalogów w celu samoczynnego importowania list odtwarzania i plików muzycznych przy uruchomieniu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidade de sondar pastas para importar automaticamente as listas de reprodução e ficheiros de música no arranque</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidade de verificar as pastas para importar automaticamente arquivos de música e listas de músicas ao iniciar</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schopnosť prehľadávať adresáre na automatický import zoznamov skladieb a hudobných súborov pri spustení</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Samodejen uvoz seznamov predvajanja in glasbenih datotek iz preiskanih map ob zagonu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Скенирање фасцикли ради аутоматског увоза листа нумера и музичких фајлова при покретању.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Skeniranje fascikli radi automatskog uvoza lista numera i muzičkih fajlova pri pokretanju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Скенирање фасцикли ради аутоматског увоза листа нумера и музичких фајлова при покретању.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Skeniranje fascikli radi automatskog uvoza lista numera i muzičkih fajlova pri pokretanju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att söka igenom kataloger vid start för att automatiskt importera spellistor och musikfiler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість автоматичного пошуку та імпортування до збірки списків відтворення та файлів звукових даних.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAbility to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start upxx</li>
      <li>Dynamic Search Playlists that are automatically updated as fields in the collection change</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Llistes de cerques dinàmiques que s'actualitzen automàticament a mesura que canvien els camps de les col·leccions.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Dynamisk søgning-spillelister som automatisk opdateres efterhånden som samlingen ændres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Dynamic Search Playlists that are automatically updated as fields in the collection change.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Búsqueda dinámica de listas de reproducción que se actualiza automáticamente con los cambios de los campos de su colección.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Dünaamilised esitusnimekirjad, mis uuenevad automaatselt kogu väljade muutumisel</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Lejátszólisták dinamikus keresése, amelyek automatikusan frissítésre kerülnek mezőkként a gyűjtemény módosításban.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Dünaamsch Söök na Afspeellisten, de automaatsch topasst warrt, wenn sik Feller binnen de Sammeln ännern doot</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Dynamisch afspeellijsten te doorzoeken zodat velden automatisch bijgewerkt worden bij wijzigingen in de verzameling.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dynamiczne przeszukiwanie list odtwarzania, które są samoczynnie uaktualnianie jako pola przy zmianie zbioru.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Listas de Pesquisas Dinâmicas que são actualizadas automaticamente à medida que os campos da colecção mudam.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Listas de Pesquisas Dinâmicas que são atualizadas automaticamente à medida que os campos da coleção mudam.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Dynamicky hľadané zoznamy skladieb, ktoré sa automaticky aktualizujú pri zmene polí v kolekcii.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Dinamični iskalni seznami predvajanja, ki se s spremembo polj v zbirki samodejno posodabljajo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Динамичке листе нумера за претраге, које се аутоматски ажурирају како се поља у збирци мењају.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Dinamičke liste numera za pretrage, koje se automatski ažuriraju kako se polja u zbirci menjaju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Динамичке листе нумера за претраге, које се аутоматски ажурирају како се поља у збирци мењају.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Dinamičke liste numera za pretrage, koje se automatski ažuriraju kako se polja u zbirci menjaju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Spellistor med dynamisk sökning som automatiskt uppdateras när fält i samlingen ändras.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Динамічні списки пошуку, які оновлюються автоматично зі зміною у полях даних збірки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDynamic Search Playlists that are automatically updated as fields in the collection changexx</li>
      <li>A Tree View mode where playlists are automatically generated for sets of albums, artists and genres</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Un mode de vista en arbre quan les llistes de reproducció es generen automàticament per conjunts d'àlbums, artistes i gèneres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">En trævisningstilstand hvor spillelister automatisk genereres for sæt af albummer, kunstnere og genrer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">A Tree View mode where playlists are automatically generated for sets of albums, artists and genres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Una vista de árbol donde las listas de reproducción se generan automáticamente por conjuntos de álbumes, artistas y géneros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Puuvaade, kus albumitele, esitajatele ja žanritele luuakse automaatselt esitusnimekirjad</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Egy fanézet mód, ahol a lejátszólisták automatikusan kerülnek előállításra albumok, előadók és műfajok halmazához.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">En Boomansicht, över de sik Afspeellisten automaatsch för Setten vun Albums, Künstlers un Musikoorden opstellen laat</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Een boomstructuurweergave waar afspeellijsten automatisch gegenereerd worden voor sets van albums, artiesten en genres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Tryb widoku drzewa, w którym listy odtwarzania są samoczynnie tworzone dla zestawów albumów, wykonawców i gatunków.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um modo em Árvore, onde as listas são geradas automaticamente para determinados conjuntos de álbuns, artistas e géneros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Um modo de exibição em árvore, onde as listas de músicas são geradas automaticamente para determinados conjuntos de álbuns, artistas e gêneros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Režim stromového zobrazenia, kde sa automaticky generujú zoznamy skladieb pre sady albumov, umelcov a žánrov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Način drevesnega pogleda, v katerem so seznami predvajanja samodejno ustvarjeni za nabor albumov, izvajalcev in zvrsti.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Режим приказа стабла, где се листе нумера аутоматски генеришу по скуповима албума, извођача и жанрова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Režim prikaza stabla, gde se liste numera automatski generišu po skupovima albuma, izvođača i žanrova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Режим приказа стабла, где се листе нумера аутоматски генеришу по скуповима албума, извођача и жанрова.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Režim prikaza stabla, gde se liste numera automatski generišu po skupovima albuma, izvođača i žanrova.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">En trädvy där spellistor automatiskt skapas för uppsättningar av album, artister och genrer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Режим ієрархічного перегляду, у якому списки відтворення створюються автоматично за наборами альбомів, виконавців та жанрів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxA Tree View mode where playlists are automatically generated for sets of albums, artists and genresxx</li>
      <li>Playlist history to indicate which files have been played and when</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Historial de llistes de reproducció per indicar quins fitxers s'han reproduït i quan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Spillelistehistorik som indikerer hvilke filer der er blevet afspillet og hvornår.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Playlist history to indicate which files have been played and when.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Un historial de reproducción que le indica qué archivos han sido reproducidos y cuándo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Esitusnimekirja ajalugu, mis näitab, milliseid faile ja millal on esitatud</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Lejátszólista előzmények annak jelölésére, hogy mely fájlok lettek már lejátszva és mikor.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Afspeellist-Vörgeschicht, över de sik wiesen lett, welk Dateien Du wannehr afspeelt hest</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Geschiedenis van afspeellijsten om aan te geven welke bestanden zijn afgespeeld en wanneer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Historia list odtwarzania do wskazania, które pliki i kiedy zostały odtworzone.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um histórico da lista de reprodução que indica quais os ficheiros que foram reproduzidos e quando.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Um histórico da lista de músicas que indica quais arquivos foram reproduzidos e quando.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">História playlistu na indikáciu, ktoré súbory boli prehrané a kedy.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zgodovina seznamov predvajanja, iz katere je razvidno katere datoteke ste predvajali in kdaj ste to storili.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Историјат листа нумера, који показује који су се фајлови пуштали и када.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Istorijat lista numera, koji pokazuje koji su se fajlovi puštali i kada.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Историјат листа нумера, који показује који су се фајлови пуштали и када.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Istorijat lista numera, koji pokazuje koji su se fajlovi puštali i kada.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Spellistehistorik som anger vilka filer som har spelats och när.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Журнал списку відтворення, у якому зберігаються дані щодо того, які файли було відтворено і коли це сталося.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaylist history to indicate which files have been played and whenxx</li>
      <li>Inline search for filtering the list of visible items</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cerca en línia pel filtrar la llista d'elements visibles.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Indlejret søgning til filtrering af synlige elementer i listen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Inline search for filtering the list of visible items.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Búsqueda bajo control para filtrar la lista de los elementos visibles.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Reasisene otsing nähtavate elementide nimekirja filtreerimiseks</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Beágyazott keresés a látható elemek listájának szűréséhez.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Binnenreegs-Söök, mit de sik de List vun sichtbor Indrääg filtern lett</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Inline zoeken voor het filteren van de lijst met zichtbare items.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie w treści do odfiltrowywania spisu widocznych elementów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pesquisa incorporada para filtrar a lista de itens visíveis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquisa incorporada para filtrar a lista de itens visíveis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Inline hľadanie pre filtrovanie zoznamu viditeľných položiek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Znotrajvrstično iskanje po seznamu vidnih predmetov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Уткана претрага за филтрирање листе видљивих ставки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Utkana pretraga za filtriranje liste vidljivih stavki.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Уткана претрага за филтрирање листе видљивих ставки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Utkana pretraga za filtriranje liste vidljivih stavki.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sökning på plats för filtrering av listan med synliga objekt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вбудована можливість пошуку для фільтрування списку показаних записів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInline search for filtering the list of visible itemsxx</li>
      <li>The ability to guess tag information based on the track's file name</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">La capacitat d'estimar la informació de les etiquetes basada en el nom de fitxer de la peça.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Mulighed for at gætte mærkeinformation baseret på sporets filnavn.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">The ability to guess tag information based on the track's file name.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">La habilidad de adivinar metadatos basada en los nombres de los archivos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Oskus oletada silditeavet pala failinime põhjal</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Címkeinformációk kitalálásának képessége a szám fájlneve alapján.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann Slötelwöör ut dat Stück sien Dateinaam raden</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">De mogelijkheid om tag-informatie te raden op basis van de bestandsnaam van de track.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość odgadywania informacji znacznika na podstawie nazwy pliku utworu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A capacidade de adivinhar a informação das marcas com base no nome do ficheiro da faixa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">A capacidade de adivinhar a informação das etiquetas com base no nome do arquivo da faixa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schopnosť uhádnutia informácie tagu založený na názve súboru skladby.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Ugibanje oznak glede na ime zvočne datoteke.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Могућност погађања ознака према имену фајла нумере.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnost pogađanja oznaka prema imenu fajla numere.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућност погађања ознака према имену фајла нумере.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnost pogađanja oznaka prema imenu fajla numere.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att gissa tagginformation baserat på spårets filnamn.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість вгадування міток на основі даних щодо назви файла композиції.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThe ability to guess tag information based on the track's file namexx</li>
      <li>File renamer that can rename files based on the tag content</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Reanomenador de fitxers que pot reanomenar fitxers basat en el contingut de l'etiqueta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Filomdøber som kan omdøbe filer baseret på mærkeindholdet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">File renamer that can rename files based on the tag content.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Un cambiador de nombres de archivo que puede renombrar archivos basándose en el contenido de sus metadatos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Failide nime muutmise tööriist, mis võib failinimesid muuta sildi sisu põhjal</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Fájlátnevező, amely képes a címketartalom alapján átnevezni fájlokat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Ümnömer, de Dateien na ehr Slötelwöör ümnömen kann</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Bestandshernoeming die kan bestanden kan hernoemen gebaseerd op de inhoud van de tag.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie zmiany nazwy pliku, które może zmienić nazwę pliku na podstawie treści znacznika.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um sistema de mudança de nomes dos ficheiros com base no conteúdo das marcas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Um sistema que pode renomear os arquivos com base no conteúdo das etiquetas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Premenovač súborov, ktorý vie premenovať súbory podľa obsahu tagu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Preimenovalnik datotek, ki preimenuje glede na vsebino oznake.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Преименовање фајлова на основу садржаја ознака.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Preimenovanje fajlova na osnovu sadržaja oznaka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Преименовање фајлова на основу садржаја ознака.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Preimenovanje fajlova na osnovu sadržaja oznaka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Byte av filnamn som kan byta namn på filer baserat på tagginnehåll.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Засіб перейменування файлів, який може перейменувати файли на основі даних міток.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFile renamer that can rename files based on the tag contentxx</li>
      <li>Tag reading and editing support for many formats including ID3v1, ID3v2 and Ogg Vorbis</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Implementa la lectura i edició d'etiquetes per molts formats incloent ID3v1, ID3v2 i Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Understøttelse af mærkelæsning og -redigering af mange formater inklusiv ID3v1, ID3v2 og Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Tag reading and editing support for many formats including ID3v1, ID3v2 and Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Leer y editar metadatos en varios formatos incluyendo ID3v1, ID3v2 y Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Siltide lugemise ja muutmise toetus paljude vormingute jaoks, sealhulgas ID3v1, ID3v2 ja Ogg Vorbis</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Címkeolvasás és szerkesztés támogatás számos formátumhoz, beleértve az ID3v1, az ID3v2 és az Ogg Vorbis formátumokat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann Slötelwöör mit vele Formaten lesen un bewerken, so as ID3v1, ID3v2 un Ogg-Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor lezen van tags en bewerken voor vele formaten inclusief ID3v1, ID3v2 en Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa odczytu i zmieniania znaczników dla wielu formatów zaliczając do nich: ID3v1, ID3v2 oraz Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para a leitura e edição de marcas em vários formatos, incluindo o ID3v1, ID3v2 e Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para leitura e edição de etiquetas em vários formatos, incluindo o ID3v1, ID3v2 e Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Podpora čítania a úpravy tagov pre veľa formátov vrátane ID3v1, ID3v2 a Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Branje in pisanje oznak ID3v1, ID3v2, Ogg Vorbis ter drugih.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за читање и уређивање ознака за многе формате, укључујући ИД3 в1 и в2, и ОГГ Ворбис.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za čitanje i uređivanje oznaka za mnoge formate, uključujući ID3 v1 i v2, i OGG Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за читање и уређивање ознака за многе формате, укључујући ИД3 в1 и в2, и ОГГ Ворбис.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za čitanje i uređivanje oznaka za mnoge formate, uključujući ID3 v1 i v2, i OGG Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för taggläsning och redigering för många format inklusive ID3v1, ID3v2 och Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка читання та редагування міток у багатьох форматах, зокрема ID3v1, ID3v2 та Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTag reading and editing support for many formats including ID3v1, ID3v2 and Ogg Vorbisxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://juk.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=juk</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdemultimedia/juk/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/juk.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>juk</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
