<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>juk.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="nds">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Џук</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Џук</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxJuKxx</name>
  <summary>Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Reproductor musical</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Přehrávač hudby</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Musikafspiller</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Audio-Wiedergabe</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Muusikamängija</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Musiikkisoitin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Zenelejátszó</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nds">Musikafspeler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Muziekspeler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Odtwarzacz muzyki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Leitor de Música</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Reprodutor de músicas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Prehrávač hudby</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Glasbeni predvajalnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Музички плејер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Muzički plejer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Музички плејер</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Muzički plejer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Musikspelare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Музичний програвач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxMusic Playerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>JuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El JuK és una aplicació de màquina de discos musicals, que accepta col·leccions de fitxers d'àudio MP3, Ogg Vorbis, i FLAC. Permet editar les "etiquetes" dels fitxers d'àudio, i gestionar les col·leccions i les llistes de reproducció. De fet, els seu focus principal és en la gestió de la música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">JuK er et lydjukebox-program, som understøtter samlinger af MP3-, Ogg Vorbis- og FLAC-lydfiler. Den lader dig redigere "mærkerne" i dine lydfiler og håndtere din samling og spillelister. Dens hovedfokus er faktisk på musikhåndtering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">JuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">JuK es una aplicación jukebox de audio, que soporta colecciones de archivos MP3, Ogg Vorbis y FLAC. Le permite editar los "tags" de sus archivos de audio, y administrar sus colecciones y listas de reproducción. Su principal cometido, de hecho, es administrar la música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">JuK on helifailide muusikamängija, mis toetab MP3, Ogg Vorbise ja FLAC-i vormingut. See võimaldab muuta helifailide "silte" ning hallata muusikakogusid ja esitusnimekirju. Õigupoolest ongi rakenduse rõhk eelkõige muusika haldamisel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A JuK egy zenedoboz alkalmazás, amely támogatja MP3, Ogg Vorbis és FLAC hangfájlok gyűjteményeit. Lehetővé teszi a hangfájlok „címkéinek” szerkesztését, és a gyűjtemények, illetve lejátszólisták kezelését. A fő célja valójában a zenekezelés.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">JuK is en Musikkist-Programm, dat Sammeln vun MP3-, Ogg-Vorbis- un FLAC-Klangdateien bruken kann. Du kannst dor de Slötelwöör („Tags“) vun Dien Dateien mit bewerken un Dien Sammeln un Afspeellisten mit plegen. Egens liggt em sien Fokus redig op de Musikpleeg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">JuK is een jukebox toepassing voor geluid, die verzamelingen van MP3, Ogg Vorbis en FLAC geluidsbestanden ondersteunt. Het stelt u in staat om de "tags" van uw geluidsbestanden te bewerken en uw verzameling en afspeellijsten te beheren. De focus is in feite op beheer van muziek.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">JuK jest programem szafy grającej, obsługującym zbiory MP3, Ogg Vorbis oraz pliki dźwiękowe FLAC. Umożliwia edytowanie "znaczników" plików dźwiękowych i zarządzanie zbiorami oraz listami odtwarzania. Jednak jego głównym celem jest zarządzanie muzyką.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O JuK é uma aplicação de reprodução de música, suportando colecções de ficheiros de áudio em MP3, Ogg Vorbis e FLAC. Permite-lhe editar as "marcas" dos seus ficheiros de áudio, gerir a sua colecção e as suas listas de reprodução. O seu foco principal é, de facto, a gestão de música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">JuK é um aplicativo para reprodução de músicas, com suporte a coleções de arquivos de áudio MP3, Ogg Vorbis e FLAC. Permite-lhe editar as etiquetas "tags" dos seus arquivos de áudio, gerenciar sua coleção e suas listas de músicas. Seu foco principal é, de fato, o gerenciamento de músicas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">JuK je aplikácia hudobného jukeboxu, podporujúca kolekcie MP3, Ogg Vorbis a FLAC audio súborov. Umožní vám upraviť tagy vašich audio súborov a spravovať vašu kolekciu a zoznamy skladieb. Jeho hlavné zameranie je správa hudby.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">JuK je predvajalnik glasbe, ki podpira zbirke zvočnih datotek MP3, Ogg Vorbis in FLAC. Omogoča urejanje "oznak" vaših zvočnih datotek ter upravljanje zbirk in seznamov predvajanj. Glavni name programa je upravljanje glasbe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Џук је програм за виртуелни џубокс. Подржава збирке МП3, ОГГ, ворбис и ФЛАЦ аудио фајлова. Даје вам да уређујете „ознаке“ аудио фајлова, и управљате збиркама и листама нумера. Тежиште му је, у ствари, на управљању музиком.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Juk je program za virtuelni džuboks. Podržava zbirke MP3, OGG, Vorbis i FLAC audio fajlova. Daje vam da uređujete „oznake“ audio fajlova, i upravljate zbirkama i listama numera. Težište mu je, u stvari, na upravljanju muzikom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Џук је програм за виртуелни џубокс. Подржава збирке МП3, ОГГ, ворбис и ФЛАЦ аудио фајлова. Даје вам да уређујете „ознаке“ аудио фајлова, и управљате збиркама и листама нумера. Тежиште му је, у ствари, на управљању музиком.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Juk je program za virtuelni džuboks. Podržava zbirke MP3, OGG, Vorbis i FLAC audio fajlova. Daje vam da uređujete „oznake“ audio fajlova, i upravljate zbirkama i listama numera. Težište mu je, u stvari, na upravljanju muzikom.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Juk är ett Jukebox-program, som stöder samlingar av MP3, Ogg Vorbis och FLAC ljudfiler. Det låter dig redigera "taggarna" i ljudfilerna, och hantera samlingen och spellistor. Dess huvudfokus är just musikhantering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">JuK — програма для відтворення музики, у якій передбачено підтримку роботи зі звуковими файлами у форматах MP3, Ogg Vorbis та FLAC. Програма допоможе вам у редагуванні міток ваших звукових файлів, керуванні вашою збіркою та списками відтворення. Основним її призначенням, фактично, є керування музичними даними.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxJuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Szolgáltatások:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nds">Markmalen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cechy:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Collection list and multiple user defined playlists</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Llista de col·leccions i múltiples llistes de reproducció definides per usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Samlingsliste og flere brugerdefinerede spillelister</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Collection list and multiple user defined playlists</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Listas de colecciones y listas de reproducción definidas por múltiples usuarios</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Muusikakogu nimekiri ja paljud kasutaja loodud esitusnimekirjad</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Gyűjteménylista és több felhasználó által megadott lejátszólista</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Sammelnlist un en Reeg Bruker-Afspeellisten</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verzamelingenlijst en afspeellijsten voor meerdere gebruikers</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Spisy zbiorów i wiele list odtwarzania określonych przez użytkownika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Lista de colecções e várias listas de reprodução definidas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Lista de coleções e várias listas de músicas definidas pelo usuário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zoznam kolekcií a viacnásobné používateľom definované zoznamy skladieb</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Seznam zbirk in več uporabniško določenih seznamov predvajanja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Листа збирки и више кориснички дефинисаних листа нумера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Lista zbirki i više korisnički definisanih lista numera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Листа збирки и више кориснички дефинисаних листа нумера.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Lista zbirki i više korisnički definisanih lista numera.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Samlingslista och flera användardefinierade spellistor.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Список збірки та декілька визначених користувачем списків відтворення.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCollection list and multiple user defined playlistsxx</li>
      <li>Ability to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start up</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Capacitat d'explorar directoris per importar automàticament llistes de reproducció i fitxers de música en iniciar-se</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Kan scanne mapper for automatisk at importere spillelister og musikfiler ved opstart</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Ability to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start up</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Capacidad de escanear directorios para importar listas de reproducción y archivos de música automáticamente al iniciar el programa</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Oskus uurida kohe käivitamisel läbi katalooge ja importida sealt esitusnimekirju ja muusikafaile</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Könyvtárak átvizsgálásának képessége zenefájlok és lejátszólisták automatikus importálásához a program indulásakor</li>
      <li xml:lang="nds">Kann Ornern  bi't Starten automaatsch op Afspeellisten un Musikdateien dörkieken</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheid om bij opstarten mappen te scannen om automatisch afspeellijsten en muziekbestanden te importeren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Możliwość przeszukiwania katalogów w celu samoczynnego importowania list odtwarzania i plików muzycznych przy uruchomieniu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidade de sondar pastas para importar automaticamente as listas de reprodução e ficheiros de música no arranque</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Capacidade de verificar as pastas para importar automaticamente arquivos de música e listas de músicas ao iniciar</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schopnosť prehľadávať adresáre na automatický import zoznamov skladieb a hudobných súborov pri spustení</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Samodejen uvoz seznamov predvajanja in glasbenih datotek iz preiskanih map ob zagonu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Скенирање фасцикли ради аутоматског увоза листа нумера и музичких фајлова при покретању.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Skeniranje fascikli radi automatskog uvoza lista numera i muzičkih fajlova pri pokretanju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Скенирање фасцикли ради аутоматског увоза листа нумера и музичких фајлова при покретању.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Skeniranje fascikli radi automatskog uvoza lista numera i muzičkih fajlova pri pokretanju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att söka igenom kataloger vid start för att automatiskt importera spellistor och musikfiler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість автоматичного пошуку та імпортування до збірки списків відтворення та файлів звукових даних.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAbility to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start upxx</li>
      <li>Dynamic Search Playlists that are automatically updated as fields in the collection change</li>
      <li>A Tree View mode where playlists are automatically generated for sets of albums, artists and genres</li>
      <li>Playlist history to indicate which files have been played and when</li>
      <li>Inline search for filtering the list of visible items</li>
      <li>The ability to guess tag information based on the track's file name</li>
      <li>File renamer that can rename files based on the tag content</li>
      <li>Tag reading and editing support for many formats including ID3v1, ID3v2 and Ogg Vorbis</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://juk.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=juk</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdemultimedia/juk/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/juk.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>juk</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
