<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>juk.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Juk</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">JuK</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxJuKxx</name>
  <summary>Music Player</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Muziekspeler</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Leitor de Música</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Musikspelare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Музичний програвач</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxMusic Playerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>JuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O JuK é uma aplicação de reprodução de música, suportando colecções de ficheiros de áudio em MP3, Ogg Vorbis e FLAC. Permite-lhe editar as "marcas" dos seus ficheiros de áudio, gerir a sua colecção e as suas listas de reprodução. O seu foco principal é, de facto, a gestão de música.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Juk är ett Jukebox-program, som stöder samlingar av MP3, Ogg Vorbis och FLAC ljudfiler. Det låter dig redigera "taggarna" i ljudfilerna, och hantera samlingen och spellistor. Dess huvudfokus är just musikhantering.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">JuK — програма для відтворення музики, у якій передбачено підтримку роботи зі звуковими файлами у форматах MP3, Ogg Vorbis та FLAC. Програма допоможе вам у редагуванні міток ваших звукових файлів, керуванні вашою збіркою та списками відтворення. Основним її призначенням, фактично, є керування музичними даними.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxJuK is an audio jukebox application, supporting collections of MP3, Ogg Vorbis, and FLAC audio files. It allows you to edit the "tags" of your audio files, and manage your collection and playlists. It's main focus, in fact, is on music management.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Características:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Collection list and multiple user defined playlists</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Lista de colecções e várias listas de reprodução definidas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Samlingslista och flera användardefinierade spellistor.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Список збірки та декілька визначених користувачем списків відтворення.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCollection list and multiple user defined playlistsxx</li>
      <li>Ability to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start up</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Capacidade de sondar pastas para importar automaticamente as listas de reprodução e ficheiros de música no arranque</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att söka igenom kataloger vid start för att automatiskt importera spellistor och musikfiler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість автоматичного пошуку та імпортування до збірки списків відтворення та файлів звукових даних.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAbility to scan directories to automatically import playlists and music files on start upxx</li>
      <li>Dynamic Search Playlists that are automatically updated as fields in the collection change.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Listas de Pesquisas Dinâmicas que são actualizadas automaticamente à medida que os campos da colecção mudam.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Spellistor med dynamisk sökning som automatiskt uppdateras när fält i samlingen ändras.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Динамічні списки пошуку, які оновлюються автоматично зі зміною у полях даних збірки.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDynamic Search Playlists that are automatically updated as fields in the collection change.xx</li>
      <li>A Tree View mode where playlists are automatically generated for sets of albums, artists and genres.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um modo em Árvore, onde as listas são geradas automaticamente para determinados conjuntos de álbuns, artistas e géneros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">En trädvy där spellistor automatiskt skapas för uppsättningar av album, artister och genrer.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Режим ієрархічного перегляду, у якому списки відтворення створюються автоматично за наборами альбомів, виконавців та жанрів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxA Tree View mode where playlists are automatically generated for sets of albums, artists and genres.xx</li>
      <li>Playlist history to indicate which files have been played and when.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um histórico da lista de reprodução que indica quais os ficheiros que foram reproduzidos e quando.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Spellistehistorik som anger vilka filer som har spelats och när.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Журнал списку відтворення, у якому зберігаються дані щодо того, які файли було відтворено і коли це сталося.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaylist history to indicate which files have been played and when.xx</li>
      <li>Inline search for filtering the list of visible items.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pesquisa incorporada para filtrar a lista de itens visíveis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sökning på plats för filtrering av listan med synliga objekt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вбудована можливість пошуку для фільтрування списку показаних записів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInline search for filtering the list of visible items.xx</li>
      <li>The ability to guess tag information based on the track's file name.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A capacidade de adivinhar a informação das marcas com base no nome do ficheiro da faixa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Möjlighet att gissa tagginformation baserat på spårets filnamn.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Можливість вгадування міток на основі даних щодо назви файла композиції.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxThe ability to guess tag information based on the track's file name.xx</li>
      <li>File renamer that can rename files based on the tag content.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Um sistema de mudança de nomes dos ficheiros com base no conteúdo das marcas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Byte av filnamn som kan byta namn på filer baserat på tagginnehåll.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Засіб перейменування файлів, який може перейменувати файли на основі даних міток.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFile renamer that can rename files based on the tag content.xx</li>
      <li>Tag reading and editing support for many formats including ID3v1, ID3v2 and Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporte para a leitura e edição de marcas em vários formatos, incluindo o ID3v1, ID3v2 e Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöd för taggläsning och redigering för många format inklusive ID3v1, ID3v2 och Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка читання та редагування міток у багатьох форматах, зокрема ID3v1, ID3v2 та Ogg Vorbis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTag reading and editing support for many formats including ID3v1, ID3v2 and Ogg Vorbis.xx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://juk.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=juk</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/stable/en/kdemultimedia/juk/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/juk.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>juk</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
